Guide to the J. Walter Thompson Company. 35mm Microfilm Proofs, 1906-1960 and undated RL.00657
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Copy Approvals (Supplement to 16mm reel 40), 1936-1940; undated; 5
  - Pond's, 1937-1939 (Film-reel 47)
    Magazines; Danaya 1937-1938, Vanishing Cream 1938, Cold Cream 1938-1939, Glare Proof powder 1938, Cream Extra Vitamin Skin 1937-1938, Cold Cream Under Skin treatment 1937-1938
  - Standard Brands, 1936-1939 (Film-reel 47)
    Magazines; Chase & Sanborn coffee 1938-1939, Bergen cartoons 1937, Dated Coffee 1936
  - Emerson Drug Co. (Bromo-Seltzer)--Magazines, 1936-1938 (Film-reel 47)
- Car Cards, undated; 6
  - Lux Flakes, undated (Film-reel 48)
  - Fleischmann's Stox, undated (Film-reel 48)
  - Pertussin (Seeck & Kade), undated (Film-reel 48)
  - Charter Oak bread, undated (Film-reel 48)
  - Fleischmann's Stox, undated (Film-reel 48)
  - Fleischmann's Yeast for Health, undated (Film-reel 48)
  - Old Witch, undated (Film-reel 48)
  - O'Sullivan's heels, undated (Film-reel 48)
  - Aunt Jemima pancake flour, undated (Film-reel 48)
- Newspaper and Magazine Advertisements, 1930-1937; undated; 7
  - Lux toilet soap, undated (Film-reel 48)
  - Lux Flakes, undated (Film-reel 48)
  - Fleischmann's Dry Gin, 1934 (Film-reel 48)
  - Chase & Sanborn, 1934-1935 (Film-reel 48)
  - Lux Flakes, 1934 (Film-reel 48)
  - Lux toilet soap, undated (Film-reel 48)
  - Standard Brands (copyright materials; continued on reel 50), undated (Film-reel 49)
  - Lucky Strike cigarettes, 1933 (Film-reel 49)
  - Chase & Sanborn, 1931-1934 (Film-reel 49)
  - CW brand coffee, 1932-1934 (Film-reel 49)
  - Royal pudding, 1931-1934 (Film-reel 49)
  - Royal gelatine, 1934 (Film-reel 49)
  - Tenderleaf Tea, 1931-1935 (Film-reel 49)
  - Royal baking powder, 1931-1934 (Film-reel 49)
  - Fleischmann's yeast, 1930-1935 (Film-reel 49)
  - Fleischmann's Dry Gin, 1937 (Film-reel 49)
  - Chase & Sanborn, 1937 (Film-reel 49)
- Portfolios, 1914-1951; undated; 8
  - Standard Brands, Inc., undated (Film-reel 49)
  - Chase & Sanborn, 1932-1935 (Film-reel 49)
  - Royal gelatine, 1933 (Film-reel 49)
  - Chase & Sanborn, 1932 (Film-reel 49)
  - Ironized Yeast, 1932 (Film-reel 49)
  - Fleischmann's Yeast for Health, 1932 (Film-reel 49)
  - Tenderleaf Tea, 1933 (Film-reel 49)
  - Potato chips, 1933 (Film-reel 49)
  - CW brand coffee, 1932-1935 (Film-reel 49)
  - Fleischmann's Yeast for Health, 1935 (Film-reel 49)
  - Rinso, 1933 May (Film-reel 49)
  - Lux Flakes, 1933 Mar. (Film-reel 49)
  - Tenderleaf Tea, 1933-1935 (Film-reel 49)
  - Lux Flakes, undated (Film-reel 49)
  - C&S Royal vanilla pudding, 1933 (Film-reel 49)
  - Tenderleaf Tea, 1934-1935 (Film-reel 49)
  - Royal baking powder, 1934 (Film-reel 49)
  - CW brand coffee, 1932 (Film-reel 49)
  - Chase & Sanborn, 1932-1933 (Film-reel 49)
  - Royal gelatine, 1935 (Film-reel 49)
  - Royal pudding, 1932-1933 (Film-reel 49)
  - Royal gelatine, 1934 (Film-reel 49)
  - Tenderleaf Tea, 1932 (Film-reel 49)
  - Royal desserts, 1931-1933 (Film-reel 49)
  - Tenderleaf Tea, 1935 (Film-reel 49)
  - Chase & Sanborn, 1931 (Film-reel 49)
  - Royal baking powder, 1931-1935 (Film-reel 49)
  - Tenderleaf Tea, 1935 (Film-reel 49)
  - Fleischmann's Yeast for Health, 1931-1935 (Film-reel 49)
  - Lux Flakes, 1933-1934 (Film-reel 49)
  - Zenith radio, 1934 May (Film-reel 49)
  - Chase & Sanborn, 1932 (Film-reel 49)
  - Rinso, 1932 (Film-reel 49)
  - Lux Flakes, 1931 (Film-reel 49)
  - Jergens' lotion, 1937 Nov. (Film-reel 49)
  - Fleischmann's yeast, Life Begins at 40, 1937 (Film-reel 50)
  - Standard Brands, Inc., undated (Film-reel 50)
  - Fleischmann's yeast, Life Begins at 40, 1936 (Film-reel 50)
  - Royal desserts, undated (Film-reel 50)
  - Fleischmann's Yeast for Health, undated (Film-reel 50)
  - Fleischmann's yeast for animals, 1931 (Film-reel 50)
  - Chase & Sanborn, 1937 (Film-reel 50)
  - Fleischmann's Dry Gin, 1937 (Film-reel 50)
  - Tenderleaf Tea, 1937 (Film-reel 50)
  - Rinso, 1937 Mar. (Film-reel 50)
  - Fleischmann's yeast, Arthur Murray, 1937 (Film-reel 50)
  - Fleischmann's yeast, Life Begins at 40, 1937 (Film-reel 50)
  - Fleischmann's yeast for health, 1938 (Film-reel 50)
  - Royal baking powder, 1937 (Film-reel 50)
  - White Owl cigars, 1933-1937 (Film-reel 50)
  - Lux toilet soap, 1934 (Film-reel 50)
  - Fleischmann's Yeast XR, 1935 (Film-reel 50)
  - Fleischmann's yeast for dogs, 1935 (Film-reel 50)
  - Fleischmann's Yeast for health, 1934 (Film-reel 50)
  - Royal baking powder, 1934 (Film-reel 50)
  - Fleischmann's yeast, 1931-1937 (Film-reel 50)
  - American Home Products, 1939-1943 (Film-reel 51)
  - Astaire, Fred, 1946-1947 (Film-reel 51)
  - Block Drug Co., 1942-1944 (Film-reel 51)
  - Boston Globe, 1935-1943 (Film-reel 51)
  - Buxton, 1924-1951 (Film-reel 51)
  - Carter's Products, 1942-1945 (Film-reel 52)
  - Chocago Community Fund, 1937 (Film-reel 52)
  - City Baking Co., 1923-1937 (Film-reel 52)
  - Coordinator of Inter American Affairs, 1943-1945 (Film-reel 52)
  - CW brand coffee, 1930-1935 (Film-reel 52)
  - Dr. Price baking powder, 1929-1935 (Film-reel 52)
  - Fulton Sylphen, 1944-1945 (Film-reel 52)
  - General Cigar, 1933-1951 (Film-reel 53)
  - GCMI, 1948 (Film-reel 53)
  - Guiness. Arthur & Sons, 1933-1948 (Film-reel 54)
  - Lever-Vimms, 1944-1945 (Film-reel 54)
  - Lever-Vimms (trade), 1944 (Film-reel 54)
  - Martini & Rossi, 1939-1941 (Film-reel 55)
  - McFadden Publications, 1939 (Film-reel 55)
  - Nashua Manufacturing, 1947-1949 (Film-reel 55)
  - Newspapers Publishers Committee, 1940-1941 (Film-reel 55)
  - New York Dress Institute, 1940-1943 (Film-reel 56)
  - New York subways, 1942 (Film-reel 56)
  - Northam Warren, 1937-1944 (Film-reel 57)
  - Northam Warren (Cutex), 1916-1927 (Film-reel 57)
  - Northam Warren (Cutex), 1928-1937 (Film-reel 58)
  - Northam Warren (Cutex), 1938-1947 (Film-reel 59)
  - Odo-ro-no, 1940-1941 (Film-reel 59)
  - Old Gold (magazine advertising 1941 on reel 69), 1941-1942 (Film-reel 59)
  - OPA-WPA campaigns, 1944 (Film-reel 59)
  - Oxford University Press, 1946-1950 (Film-reel 59)
  - Pennsylvania Central Airways, 1943-1945 (Film-reel 60)
  - Petroleum Industry War Council, 1943 (Film-reel 60)
  - Planters Nuts & Chocolate Co., 1934-1944 (Film-reel 60)
  - Popular Science magazine, 1924-1930 (Film-reel 60)
  - Powers, John Robert, 1943-1945 (Film-reel 60)
  - Dr. Price baking powder, 1929-1935 (Film-reel 60)
  - Quinlan, Kathleen Mary, 1929-1940 (Film-reel 61)
  - Radio Times, 1937-1940 (Film-reel 61)
  - Ready to Serve, 1941 (Film-reel 61)
  - Reynolds Metals, 1946-1947 (Film-reel 61)
  - Rheem Manufacturing, 1941 (Film-reel 62)
  - Serfert, 1947-1948 (Film-reel 62)
  - Sharp & Dohme, 1930-1942 (Film-reel 62)
  - Sharp & Dohme, 1942-1947 (Film-reel 63)
  - Fleischmann's, 1923-1942 (Film-reel 63)
  - Chase & Sanborn, 1931-1933 (Film-reel 64)
  - Chase & Sanborn (also potato chips), 1934-1937 (Film-reel 65)
  - Chase & Sanborn, 1938-1941 (Film-reel 66)
  - Chase & Sanborn, 1942-1949 (Film-reel 67)
  - Taylor, W.A. Co., 1941-1942 (Film-reel 67)
  - Textron, 1943-1950 (Film-reel 68)
  - Toad Shipyards, 1943 (Film-reel 68)
  - U.S. Gutta Percha, 1914-1931 (Film-reel 68)
  - U.S. Gutta Percha, 1930-1942 (Film-reel 69)
  - U.S. Navy Relief vol. 1, 1942 (Film-reel 69)
  - Western Union Telegraph, 1946-1950 (Film-reel 69)
  - Old Gold, 1941 (Film-reel 69)
- Portfolios: Inactive Accounts, 1920-1955; undated; 9
  - Ballantine & Sons, 1935-1941 (Film-reel 70)
  - Ballantine & Sons, 1941-1946 (Film-reel 71)
  - Ballantine & Sons, 1947-1953 (Film-reel 72)
  - Ballantine & Sons, 1953-1955 (Film-reel 73)
  - Fanny Farmer, 1939-1950 (Film-reel 74)
  - Florida Citrus, 1950-1955 (Film-reel 75)
  - New York subways, 1942-1948 (Film-reel 75)
  - Penick & ford, 1920-1943 (Film-reel 76)
  - Radio Corporation of America (RCA) vol. 1, 1943-1944 (Film-reel 77)
  - Radio Corporation of America (RCA) vol. 1, 1943-1944 (Film-reel 78)
  - National Broadcasting Company, 1945-1946 (Film-reel 78)
  - Radio Corporation of America (RCA) America vol. 2, 1947 (Film-reel 79)
  - Radio Corporation of America (RCA) National vol. 1, 1947 (Film-reel 79)
  - RCA Victor vol. 1,2, 1947 (Film-reel 79)
  - RCA Tube Division, 1947 (Film-reel 79)
  - RCA Victor programs vol. 2, 1948 (Film-reel 80)
  - RCA Victor Division, 1948 (Film-reel 80)
  - RCA Engineering Products, 1948 (Film-reel 80)
  - RCA programs vol. 1, 1949 (Film-reel 81)
  - RCA programs vol. 2, 1949 (Film-reel 81)
  - RCA American institutional, 1948 (Film-reel 82)
  - RCA American tube, 1948 (Film-reel 82)
  - RCA Engineering Products, 1949 (Film-reel 82)
  - RCA institutional, 1949 (Film-reel 82)
  - RCA Victor records, 1942 (Film-reel 82)
  - RCA home instruments vol. 1, 1949 (Film-reel 82)
  - RCA home instruments vol. 2, 1949 (Film-reel 82)
  - RCA Victor (4 vol.s), 1950 (Film-reel 83)
  - RCA Tube Division, 1950 (Film-reel 84)
  - RCA programs vol. 1, 1950 (Film-reel 84)
  - RCA programs vol. 2, 1950 (Film-reel 84)
  - RCA American institutional, 1950 (Film-reel 84)
  - RCA home instruments, 1953 (Film-reel 84)
  - RCA newspaper, undated (Film-reel 84)
  - RCA insertion schedules, 1946 June 24-1947 Dec. 27 (Film-reel 85)
  - Reynolds Metals, 1943-1945 (Film-reel 86)
  - Scranton Lace Co., 1943-1950 (Film-reel 86)
  - Textron, 1943-1944 (Film-reel 86)
  - Document for Pat Nichols, undated (Film-reel 86)
- Portfolios: Discontinued Accounts, 1931-1960; undated; 10
  - American Cancer Society, 1953-1954 (Film-reel 87)
  - Aquascutum, 1955-1959 (Film-reel 87)
  - Boyle-Midway, 1958-1959 (Film-reel 87)
  - Buitoni, 1955-1957 (Film-reel 87)
  - Burlington Mills, 1956-1957 (Film-reel 87)
  - Carter's Ink, 1931-1947; 1949-1951 (Film-reel 87)
  - Church and Dwight, 1949-1959 (Film-reel 87)
  - Ciba, 1956-1957 (Film-reel 87)
  - Columbia Mills, 1951-1955 (Film-reel 87)
  - Crompton, 1957-1958 (Film-reel 87)
  - Devoe and Reynolds, 1955-1958 (Film-reel 88)
  - Farrell Lines, 1949-1959 (Film-reel 88)
  - Fieldcrest, 1956-1958 (Film-reel 88)
  - Good Housekeeping, 1939-1942 (Film-reel 88)
  - E.F. Hutton, 1956 (Film-reel 88)
  - Johns-Manville, 1931 Jan.-1933 Jan. (Film-reel 88)
  - Johns-Manville, 1933 June-1938 Nov. (Film-reel 89)
  - Johns-Manville, 1938-1942 (Film-reel 90)
  - Johns-Manville, 1942-1946 (Film-reel 91)
  - Johns-Manville, 1946-1951 (Film-reel 92)
  - Johns-Manville, 1951-1957 (Film-reel 93)
  - Johns-Manville, 1957-1959 (Film-reel 94)
  - New York Central Railroad, 1955-1959 (Film-reel 94)
  - Oneida, 1948-1960 (Film-reel 94)
  - Pacific Mills, 1956-1957 (Film-reel 94)
  - Pacific Mills, 1957-1959 (Film-reel 95)
  - Penick & Ford, 1938-1939; 1944-1954 (Film-reel 95)
  - Pharmacraft, 1946-1960 (Film-reel 95)
  - RCA, 1946 (Film-reel 95)
  - Polytravel & Tours, 1955-1960 (Film-reel 95)
  - RCA, 1951-1953 (Film-reel 96)
  - Seth Thomas, 1951-1956 (Film-reel 96)
  - Shell Oil, 1932-1935 (Film-reel 96)
  - Shell Oil, 1936-1943 (Film-reel 97)
  - Shell Oil (reel missing as of 4/23/80), 1942-1951 (Film-reel 98)
  - Shell Oil, 1951-1956 (Film-reel 99)
  - Shell Oil, 1956-1959 (Film-reel 100)
  - Shell Oil, 1959-1960 (Film-reel 101)
  - Alexander Smith, 1952-1955 (Film-reel 101)
  - Staze, 1950-1955 (Film-reel 101)
  - Stouffer, 1958-1960 (Film-reel 101)
  - Sylvania, 1955-1956 (Film-reel 101)
  - Sylvania, 1956-1959 (Film-reel 102)
  - Trico, 1955-1956 (Film-reel 102)
  - United Hospital Fund, 1930-1937 (Film-reel 102)
  - Ward Baking, 1942-1947 (Film-reel 102)
  - Ward Baking, 1947-1949 (Film-reel 103)
  - J.B. Williams, 1936-1947 (Film-reel 103)
  - J.B. Williams, 1948-1957 (Film-reel 104)
  - Wool Bureau, 1954-1960 (Film-reel 104)